Guide to the National Organization for Women, New York City Chapter (NOW-NYC) Records TAM.106
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Committees, 1966-2006; 1970-2002; 19.58 Linear Feet in 41 manuscript boxes, a flat box, 3 oversized flat boxes, and 2 flat-file-folders
  - Employment Committee -- Work & Sex: How You Can Fight Sex Discrimination in Employment Booklet Project, 1978-1979 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Employment Committee -- Working Women Resources, 1977, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - ERA Committee -- Card and Bumper Sticker, 1977-1982 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - ERA Task Force, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - ERA Task Force, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - ERA Task Force, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - ERA Task Force, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - ERA Task Force, 1974-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 79, Folder 10, Box 80, Folder 1-3)
  - ERA Task Force, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - ERA Task Force, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - ERA Task Force, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - ERA Task Force, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - ERA Task Force, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - ERA Task Force -- Administrative Papers, 1981-1982 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - ERA Task Force -- "The American Way: Ratify the ERA", 1974 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - ERA Task Force -- Art for ERA, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - ERA Task Force -- "Bowling for Equality", 1980 (Box 13, Folder 10, Box 80, Folder 8)
  - ERA Task Force -- Blank Forms, undated (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - ERA Task Force -- Boycott Kit, undated (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - ERA Task Force -- Color Alerts, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - ERA Task Force -- Correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box 80, Folder 11, Box 81, Folder 1)
  - ERA Task Force -- Equality Riders Campaign, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 12, Box 81, Folder 2-4)
  - ERA Task Force -- Equality Riders Campaign -- Diaries, 1981-1982 (Box 81, Folder 5-6)
  - ERA Task Force -- Equality Riders Campaign -- Interview Questionnaires, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 1-5, Box 83, Folder 1-2)
  - ERA Task Force -- "ERA Action: Congressional Letters", 1982 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - ERA Task Force -- ERA Amendments Poster, undated (Flat-file-folder 2 Right)
  - ERA Task Force -- ERA Awareness Week Kit, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - ERA Task Force -- ERA Countdown Campaign, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - ERA Task Force -- ERA Endorsements, 1977, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - ERA Task Force -- ERA Extension and Rescission Case, 1977-1978, 1981-1982 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - ERA Task Force -- ERA House Parties, 1980, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - ERA Task Force -- ERA Merchandise Logistics, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - ERA Task Force -- ERA Missionary Project, undated (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - ERA Task Force -- ERA National Outreach Campaign Kit, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - ERA Task Force -- ERA Republican Action Kit, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - ERA Task Force -- ERA Walk, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - ERA Task Force -- Illinois Ratification Effort, 1976-1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - ERA Task Force -- Message Brigade Campaign, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - ERA Task Force -- Truth Squad Event, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - ERA Task Force -- Press Kit -- State ERA Picket, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - ERA Task Force -- Pamphlets, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - ERA Task Force -- Handwritten Notes, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - ERA Task Force -- Keep ERA Rolling Benefit, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - ERA Task Force -- Legislation, 1972, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - ERA Task Force -- Lobbying in Behalf of the ERA, 1977, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - ERA Task Force -- Mail & Petition Campaign Kit, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - ERA Task Force -- Meetings Minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - ERA Task Force -- Message Brigade, undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - ERA Task Force -- National ERA March (Washington, D.C.), undated (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - ERA Task Force -- National ERA Petition Campaign, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - ERA Task Force -- National March for ERA Ratification in Illinois, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - ERA Task Force -- NOW-NYC's 3rd Annual Round the Clock Watch for the ERA, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - ERA Task Force -- Phone Campaign, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - ERA Task Force -- Political Action Research, undated (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - ERA Task Force -- Press Clippings about the ERA, 1981-1982 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - ERA Task Force -- Press Kit, 1977-1978 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - ERA Task Force -- Press Releases, 1978-1982 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - ERA Task Force -- Resources and Information about the ERA, 1978, 1981-1984 (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
  - ERA Task Force -- Testimony of Myra K. Wolfgang Before the Senate Judiciary Committee, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - ERA Task Force -- "Who Speaks for Women?" Transcript, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - ERA Task Force -- Women Can Make the Difference, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Family Relations Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Family Relations Committee, 1980-1990 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Child Care, 1972-1974, 1983-1986 (Box 86, Folder 7-8)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Displaced Homemakers, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Directory, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Divorce, 1972-1974, 1990-1991 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Family Relations Committee -- "Divorce: New York Style", 1982 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Domestic Partnership, undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Event Flyers, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Family Life and Sex Education Curriculum, 1985-1986 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Family Relations Survey, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Joint Custody, 1985-1986 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Legal Resources, 1973, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Meeting Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Mother's Day Bill of Rights, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Parental and Medical Leave Act 1986, 1986-1987 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Press Releases, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Family Relations Committee -- Resources, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Family Relations Committee -- "Single Parenting by Choice" Program, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Family Relations Committee -- A Woman's Guide to Marriage and Divorce in New York, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Finance Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Finance Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Finance Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Finance Committee -- Audit Committee, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Finance Committee, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Finance Committee, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Finance Committee -- Resources, 1978-1979 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Friends of NOW-NYC, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising Committee, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising Committee, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising Committee, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising Committee, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Fundraising Committee, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising Committee, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Fundraising Committee, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Fundraising Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Fundraising Committee -- Commercial Products, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising Committee -- Feminist Christmas Fair, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising Committee -- Feminist Christmas Fair, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising Committee -- Feminist Christmas Fair, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising Committee -- Members and Potential Members, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Fundraising Committee -- Promotional Ideas, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - General Committee Information, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Image of Women Committee, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Image of Women Committee, 1970-1975 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Image of Women Committee, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Image of Women Committee, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Image of Women Committee, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Image of Women Committee, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Image of Women Committee, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Image of Women in Media Committee, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Image of Women Committee, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Image of Women Committee -- The Image of Women in the Advertising Media: Scrapbook, 1968-1971 (Box 15A)
  - Image of Women Committee -- Images of Women in the Mass Media, 1970 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Image of Women Committee -- Monitoring the Presentation of Women on TV, 1971-1975, 1977, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 5-6)
  - Image of Women Committee -- New York Daily News Project, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Image of Women Committee -- New York Times Project, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Image of Women Committee -- NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund (LDEF) Advertising Campaign, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Image of Women Committee -- NOW-NYC Challenges WABC and Sexism, 1970, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Image of Women Committee -- Print Ads, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Action Workers (L.A.W.) Committee, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1971-1976 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1977-1983 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- 1984 Presidential Election (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Anti-Robert Bork, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Arthur Sullivan v. NOW, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Bella Abzug, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Betty Friedan, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Civil Rights Restoration Act, 1985-1991 (Box 89, Folder 6-7)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Discrimination Against Women, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Economic Equity Act, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Events and Rally Flyers, 1969, 2004-2005 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Legislative Bills with NOW Annotations, 1989-1990 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Legislative Priorities, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Legislative Update, 1991-1992 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Lobbying, 1976-1985 (Box 90, Folder 3-4)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- New York City Alterbudget, 1986-1987 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- New York State Division of Human Rights and A11013, undated (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- NOW-New York State (NOW-NYS) State Lobby Day, Albany, N.Y., March 13, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- NOW-NYS Lobby Day, Albany, N.Y., March 13, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- NOW-NYS Lobby Day, Albany, N.Y., March 23, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Personal Opinion Messages (POMs), 1985 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Political Action, 1969 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Press Releases, 1982-1983 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Private Clubs and Discrimination, 1980-1985 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Ronald Reagan, 1980-1982 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- School for Candidates, Seneca Falls, N.Y., July 17, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Shirley Chisholm, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Special Housing Needs of Women, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Voter Registration, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- White House Inauguration Day Protest, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- WomanPower, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Women and the City: How to Use the Machinery, 1971 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Women and the Draft, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Women in Politics, 1972-1975 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Women's Rights in New York State, 1984-1986 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee -- Women's Rights Supporter Questionnaire, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Lesbian Rights Committee, 1978-1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Lesbian Rights Committee, 1978-1987 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Lesbian Rights Committee -- Event Flyers, undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Lesbian Rights Committee -- Intro1 (Gay Rights Bill), 1983 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Lesbian Sexuality Committee, undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Marriage and Family Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1972-1975 (Box 95, Folder 5-6)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee -- Child Care Tax Deduction and Elizabeth Barrett Case, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee -- Consumer Education Series, circa 1970s (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee -- Divorce Survival Kit, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee -- Equal Rights Divorce Reform Bill, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee -- Event Flyers, undated (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee -- "The Family Court: How It Is, But Not How It Should Be", 1971 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee -- Referral Resources, 1976-1978 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee -- State Conference on Marriage and Divorce, January 19-20, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee -- Task Force on Battered Wives, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee -- Women: A Political Force Conference, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Media Reform Committee, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Media Reform Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Media Reform Committee -- 1985 Virginia Slims American Women's Opinion Polls (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Abortion and the ERA, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Anti-Pornography Poster, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 208, Folder 1)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Board Members, undated (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Cable Television EEO Clause and Opposition to Cable Franchise Agreement, 1979-1981 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Cable TV Survey, circa 1980s (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Media Reform Committee -- CBS Adopt a School Program, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 101, Folder 6-7, Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Correspondence and Complaints about the Portrayal of Women in Media, 1979-1982 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Correspondence with TV Stations about Editorial Departments, 1981 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Media Reform Committee -- "Custer's Revenge" and Other Sexually Violent Video Games, 1982-1983 (Box 102, Folder 1, Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Depictions of Women in Media, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 2, Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Event Flyers, undated (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Fact Sheet, undated (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Federal Communications Commission (FCC) and Fair Treatment of Women, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Media Reform Committee -- For Your Eyes Only (James Bond film), 1981, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Fort Apache, the Bronx, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Media Reform Committee -- "Hollywood Hates Women!" Poster, 1992 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Media Reform Committee -- The Image of Women in the Advertising Media, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Media Reform Postcards Campaign, 1987-1989 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Monitoring Depictions of Women on TV, 1978, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Media Reform Committee -- NOW-NYC's Opposition to Deregulation of Broadcast and Cable Television, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Pornography, 1983-1985 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Press Releases, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Problematic Women's Jeans Advertisements, 1980-1981 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Media Reform Committee -- "Public Assistance" Board Game, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Rape Documentary, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Rated X (Documentary), 1984 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Sexist Advertising, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - Media Reform Committee -- Universal Cable TV Access, 1980-1982 (Box 102, Folder 20)
  - Membership Committee, 1966-2000 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Membership Committee, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Membership Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Membership Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Membership Committee, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Membership Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Membership Committee, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Membership Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Membership Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Membership Committee -- Membership List, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Membership Committee -- Membership Retention, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Membership Committee -- Men's Action Group, 1970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Membership Committee -- Renewals, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Membership Committee -- Renewals and Lists, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Membership Committee -- Requests for Information, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee, 1972-1988 (Box 109, Folder 3-5)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Accessible Transportation, 1985-1986 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Agendas and Meeting Minutes, 1981-1986 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- "Aging: A Woman's Issue" Conference, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Committee Information, 1979-1985 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Directory, undated (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Event Flyers, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Handwritten Notes, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Health, 1979-1986 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Housing, 1984-1986 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- List of Affiliate Groups, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Membership, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Out of the Shadows Workshop, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Oral Report to the Board, undated (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Patricia Moore, 1983-1986 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Pension Equity, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- Social Security, 1985-1986 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- "Social Security Under Siege" Program, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 15, Folder 1)
  - Mid-Life and Older Women's Issues Committee -- "A Time for Changes and Choices" Conference, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 2-3)
  - Minority Women's Issues Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Minority Women's Issues Committee, 1972-1985 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Minority Women's Issues Committee -- Combating Racism, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Minority Women's Issues Committee -- Event Flyers, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Minority Women's Issues Committee -- Resources, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Minority Women's Issues Committee -- The Success of Women and Minorities in Achieving Judicial Office, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Multicultural Issues Committee, 1991 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Multicultural Issues Committee -- Reports, 1990 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Committee, 2001 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - NOW-NYC Issues Committee -- Event Flyers, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Over-45 Committee, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Over-45 Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Over-45 Committee -- Newsletters, 1972, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Older Women's Issues Committee, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Older Women's Issues Committee, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Program Committee, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Provisional Committee on Domestic Violence, 1973-1990 (Box 111, Folder 14-15)
  - Psychology Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Psychology Committee, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Psychology Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Psychology Committee, 1973-1988 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Psychology Committee -- A Consumer's Guide to Nonsexist Therapy, 1978 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Psychology Committee -- Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Psychology Committee -- Handwritten Notes, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Psychology Committee -- Meeting Minutes, 1978-1981 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Psychology Committee -- Press Releases, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Psychology Committee -- Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Psychology Committee -- Resources, undated (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Psychology Committee -- "Sexism in Treatment" (Paper Presented at the 1st National Women in Crisis Conference), 1979 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Psychology Committee -- Survey, 1992 (Box 153, Folder 10)